<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Bijou's is the Seamless Merger of you and Elegant Accessories]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Bijou's is the Seamless Merger of you and Elegant Accessories]]></description>
        <link>http://bijousfashions.biz/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 07:57:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://bijousfashions.biz/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 07:57:15 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Women Dress,Haoricu Fall Women Fashion African Print Dress Casual Straight Print Dress]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/3d11a8d8-8f2c-464c-a52c-0fd83675e868.jpg">,<h1>Women Dress,Haoricu Fall Women Fashion African Print Dress Casual Straight Print Dress</h1>]]></description>
            <link>&lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot;  href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B01M8HUXUI/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;creativeASIN=B01M8HUXUI&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;tag=shodge915-20&amp;linkId=ff873cfa8143f751e469398539505425&quot;&gt;&lt;img border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?_encoding=UTF8&amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;ASIN=B01M8HUXUI&amp;ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;ID=AsinImage&amp;WS=1&amp;Format=_SL250_&amp;tag=shodge915-20&quot; &gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;//ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=shodge915-20&amp;l=am2&amp;o=1&amp;a=B01M8HUXUI&quot; width=&quot;1&quot; height=&quot;1&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; style=&quot;border:none !important; margin:0px !important;&quot; /&gt;</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">09594947-cf17-4566-94de-88e1165490a2</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 07:54:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[apif: Beautiful 💙 Model @melanated__godd...]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>apif: Beautiful &#x1F499; Model @melanated__godd...</h1><p>apif: Beautiful &#x1F499; Model @melanated__goddess &#x1F4F7; @akama_paul &#x2796;&#x2796;&#x2796;&#x2796;&#x2796;&#x2796;&#x2796;&#x2796;&#x2796; #headwrap #turban #prints #africanprint #queen #melanin #beauty #kente #africanfashion #fashion #accessories #ghana&#x1F1EC;&#x1F1ED; #apif #apifrocks Soooo gorgeous :-)</p><img src="http://78.media.tumblr.com/85e91512e6f6478ffe391311ea19a334/tumblr_ozeop6pHc71r24v54o1_1280.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://bijousfashions.tumblr.com/post/167895654100/apif-beautiful-model-melanatedgoddess</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">469f78dc-1f2d-403f-aae1-5a42a27765f9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 07:29:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sarahah slurps up contacts 
]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/79d59d57-029b-4637-ac51-707fee00821a.jpg">,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FWXDpCTrWdMQ%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DWXDpCTrWdMQ&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FWXDpCTrWdMQ%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=a715cf41cc93453ca338d350cd26f87b&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<h1>Sarahah slurps up contacts 
</h1>,<p>Many social media apps sink their fangs into users’ devices to
suck out their contact lists.</p>,<p>It makes sense. How else would they a) offer to hook you up with
people you know and/or b) <a href="https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2015/10/05/linkedin-set-to-pay-13-million-compensation-over-its-email-persistence/">send
a swarm of marketing email</a>&nbsp;to pester your friends?</p>,<p>It’s not only potentially useful; it has the potential to drive
your buddies insane with the resulting plague of marketing email, if
<a href="https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2013/09/24/linkedin-denies-charges-that-it-hacks-users-email/">LinkedIn’s
past pestering</a> is any indication.</p>,<p>And now, there’s a problem with the way that the latest viral
sensation app, Sarahah, siphons contact lists. Namely, it is quietly
sucking up users’ contacts, but it’s not giving them anything in
return.</p>,<p>Sarahah, the <a href="https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2017/08/11/latest-viral-sensation-app-sarahah-raises-concerns-about-cyberbullying/">latest
people-rating app,</a> bills itself as a way to “receive honest
feedback” from friends and employees… anonymously. How the
“anonymous” part of the equation jibes with showing users who
else they know on the app is anybody’s guess.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/WXDpCTrWdMQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">e340de7c-f7da-4d48-9cff-eed2b85c3616</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 00:35:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Make Money as a Writer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How to Make Money as a Writer</h1><p>English Literature professor Dr Tyra Seldon teaches you how to make money as a writer</p><img src="https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/w8C0rat3RUeQ5Xet2Hta"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://theblackbusinessschool.com/p/how-to-make-a-living-as-a-writer/?product_id=286092&amp;coupon_code=FIRSTMONTHFREE061017&amp;a_aid=57465b6d9f52d&amp;a_bid=5340dcb8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3a7e60f5-da40-49a8-be62-3e446b89ca5f</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 18:08:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[5 Fearless Black Female Warriors Throughout History]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>African women of antiquity were legendary for their beauty and power.  
Especially great were the Queens of Ethiopia; Queen of Sheba (960 B.C.),
 Candace of Meroe and her defeat of Alexander the Great (332 B.C.), 
Amanirenas, Amanishakhete, Nawidemak, Amanitore (Acts 8:26-40), 
Shanakdakh, and Malegereabar.</p>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2Fw3wNMPaXofY%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3Dw3wNMPaXofY&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2Fw3wNMPaXofY%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/w3wNMPaXofY</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">efb6a5ba-0e61-49be-ba79-f936357c64aa</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 04:15:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bangwa Queen]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ea8061c7-61e0-42f2-ba41-1bd2ca1aeaf5.jpg" title="Bangwa Queen">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7b0350f5-cd0c-48e5-bb89-fbc6a6c4c37d.jpg">,<p>“There's a clear link between an African mask, a romantic piece of furniture and a Matisse painting. Each is mysterious and strong, two essential qualities for happiness and beauty', said Helena Rubinstein to anybody who questioned her reasoning for her love of artwork. As one of her favorite pastimes, the beauty queen relished collecting fine pieces of art and was a patron for the industry.</p>,<p>A woman ahead of her time</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0d10b1c9-d1bc-44e6-8b12-04b3623ccdc0.jpg" title="Helena Rubinstein in her home African Library ">,<p>On top of being considered a bold pioneer in many fields, Helena Rubinstein also had a real passion for art and quickly became an esteemed collector. Although she was known to snap up large numbers of artwork in the blink of an eye, she did so with precision and was selective about her choices. Attracted by avant-garde pieces and African art, she was one of the first individuals globally to procure and display them in her many apartments. One of her favorite pieces was the Bangwa Queen, a Cameroonian statuette dating from the mid-18th century. Her primitive art pieces were so famous that the New York Museum of Modern Art borrowed her collection as part of a major traveling exhibition in 1935. As usual, her vision for future trends and valuable art was spot-on; African Art is now one of the most collected genres on the market.</p>,<p>Helena Rubinstein, the patron</p>,<p>The beauty expert did not consider herself a collector. She preferred to support and launch artist's careers, trusting her instincts more than what was considered fashionable at the time. Throughout her life, she created various art foundations and set aside part of her fortune for patronage. It is thanks to her donations that the Helena Rubinstein Pavilion for Contemporary Art museum opened its doors to the public in 1959 in Tel Aviv, Israel.</p>,<p>A patron from the very beginning, Helena Rubinstein was linked to some of the most prestigious 20th century artists, mixing her admiration of their work with true, lasting friendships. She was also the muse of many famous painters and sculptors from around the world. She expressed her passion and love of art wherever she went and in many of her own projects.</p>,<p>ARTS/ARTIFACTS</p>,<p>ARTS/ARTIFACTS; From Africa, a Sophisticated Lady of Rhythm</p>,<p>By RITA REIF </p>,<p>Published: April 30, 1995</p>,<p>AS MOST COLLECTORS KNOW, THE RIGHT owner's name in the pedigree of an object adds luster to its value: the Duchess of Windsor in emeralds and pearls, Andy Warhol in cookie jars, the Rothschilds in 18th-century French furniture. </p>,<p>To aficionados and auctioneers of African art, today's magical name is Helena Rubinstein. Twice in this century, an exuberant Cameroon carving of a Bangwa queen, owned for 30 years by the cosmetics tycoon, brought the highest price ever for African art at Sotheby's auctions in New York: $29,000 in 1966 and $3.4 million in 1990, the current record. </p>,<p>Now another important African work from the Rubinstein collection, a Senufo sculpture of a woman from the Ivory Coast, will go on sale, on Friday at Christie's in New York. The piece is a century-old ceremonial work, a three-foot-high "rhythm pounder" that was used in ritual dances. It was also in the Rubinstein estate sale in 1966 (Rubinstein had died at age 94) and was bought then by Sidney Janis, a Manhattan art dealer, for $27,000. Today, Christie's looks for the piece to bring $1.5 million to $2.5 million. </p>,<p>Cameroon-Nweh/Bangwa People: Origin of modern humans? </p>,<p>March 31, 2013 </p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9f311e5c-b47a-45ad-a2cb-d9af166e50c0.jpg" title="Geographical Location of Cameroon">,<p>Cameroon-Nweh/Bangwa, Mbo Yemba people: origin of modern humans?</p>,<p>A new study published in March 2013 in the&nbsp;American Journal of Human Genetics,has placed the &nbsp;Bangwa ,</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/08e6b678-3b3e-4773-95f6-df97059427e5.jpg">,<p>the&nbsp;Mbo and &nbsp;the Yemba people based &nbsp;in southwest and west Regions of Cameroon &nbsp;at the origin of modern humans. This discovery was developed and published by scientists and geneticists of the University of Arizona, USA after the analysis of the DNA of an Africa American who submitted his DNA for tests so as to trace his family roots. They found that the male Y-chromosome found in this individual dates back to 338,000 years.&nbsp;Y chromosome are the hereditary factor that determine male sex.&nbsp;Unlike autosomal chromosomes, the Y and Mitochondrial&nbsp;chromosome&nbsp;do not mix during meiosis meaning that except for mutations, the Y haplotype remains constant from generation to generation thus enables an&nbsp;analysis to trace family roots. This findings&nbsp;pushes&nbsp;back by 138,000 years, the time that scientist previously believed modern humans first evolved. It’s worth noting that this discovery and subsequent publication was a completion of the work of&nbsp;Bonnie. Schrack, citizen scientist, Stanislaw&nbsp; Pietrzak, a polish Catholic priest and T. Krahn,&nbsp; who owns a testing laboratory in Houston Texas.</p>,<p>&nbsp;The study was headed by University of Arizona Professor Fernando Mendez and colleagues. They also analyzed more than 240.000 base pairs of the Y chromosome before finally publishing their findings in the&nbsp;American Journal of Human Genetics&nbsp;early 2013.</p>,<p>This discovery also pushes back the time when modern humans evolved from early hominids by 70% and put the people of Fontem (Bangwa/Newh), the Mbo and Yemba people at the origin of modern humans at least for now. Samples from these individuals matched the Y chromosome DNA of 11 men (ancestors), some of whose names according to Stanislaw Pietrzak include:&nbsp;</p>,<p>Mbekem b. 1875, Fontem</p>,<p>Atabong b. 1862, &gt; Tanjuateh b. 1895, Fontem, Azi</p>,<p>Mbenzefeh b. 1888, Fontem</p>,<p>Ncheanzach TABI b. 1894, Mamfe</p>,<p>Tatuch b. 1903, Fontem</p>,<p>Tatych b. 1903, Fontem</p>,<p>Tatuch Anutechia b.1885, Fontem</p>,<p>George Techoukwi b. 1895, Fontem</p>,<p>Forethia b. 1885, Fontem</p>,<p>Emetem b. 1858, &gt; Njualem Nwedlataw, Fontem</p>,<p>Aminde b. 1897, Fontem</p>,<p>Atemkeng b. 1846, &gt; Thomas Ngwondong, Fontem, Lewoh.</p>,<p>Mbeh NtonGhawaH b. 1905, Fontem</p>,<p>Bangwa people, who&nbsp; are also known as the Nweh people comprise all villages in Fontem subdivision such as Lebang, Essoh-Attah and others in Alou sub division such as, Lewoh,&nbsp; Nwametaw, Ndungated etc in &nbsp;Lebialem, Cameroon, Africa. &nbsp;Bangwa &nbsp;Mbo and Yemba ( bamileke) &nbsp;people all share common boundaries. They also have &nbsp;similar&nbsp;cultural heritage.</p>,<p>This is what Dr Schrack had to say “Another thing I might mention is that our African American project members are a far closer match to the Bangwa people, whose&nbsp;haplotypes are found in the SMGF database...than to the Mbo who were sequenced. The Bangwa and Mbo are close neighbors, and rivals...when talking about who our project member's kinfolk in Africa might be, it's a far better chance they're Bangwa, from&nbsp;Fontem, Lebialem, than Mbo. We found two SNPs in our project members that were negative in the Mbo -- perhaps they'd be found positive if Bangwa were tested.&nbsp;&nbsp;Bonnie Schrack” Source&nbsp;http://www.yourgeneticgenealogist.com/2013/03/citizen-science-helps-to-rewrite-y.html</p>,<p>Ever since this discovery, Polish clergy and philanthropist&nbsp;Stanislaw Pietrzak has been mobilizing funds to assist people of Y chromosome or AOO Adam in the Fontem/Nweh area.&nbsp;The funds which have been and continue to be&nbsp;channeled&nbsp;to Agendia &nbsp;Aloysius, have been used&nbsp;to help needy families subsidise the education of theirs kids&nbsp;as well as pay for some medical bills.</p>,<p>&nbsp;ALOYSIUS&nbsp;AGENDIA</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://bijousfashions.biz/bangwa-queen/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">02880685-7eb7-43cf-9ffd-640c602b25c7</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 04:38:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[See how Black Panther and his new team come together in Harlem!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/cd37cc8d-0c75-477e-b66d-6ede189e8213.jpg">,<h2>See how Black Panther and his new team come together in Harlem!</h2>,<p>Butch Guice opens up his “Black Panther &amp; The Crew” sketchbook for a sneak peek at mystery and mayhem in Harlem: <a href="http://bit.ly/2lTOpGx">http://bit.ly/2lTOpGx</a></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0adbc797-a5c5-4871-9ead-a5ea7ee6770a.gif">,<p>The death of civil rights leader Ezra Keith sends shockwaves through his Harlem community and beyond. In fact, the mystery of his death in police custody proves so astonishing that a group of famous heroes comes together to figure out what happened.</p>,<p>That’s how <a href="https://comicstore.marvel.com/Black-Panther-And-The-Crew-2017/comics-series/89688">BLACK PANTHER AND THE CREW</a> kicks off from writers Ta-Nehisi Coates and Yona Harvey along with artist Butch Guice. The King of Wakanda finds himself joined by Misty Knight, Luke Cage, Manifold, and his ex-wife Storm as they all seek to find out what happened to Keith.</p>,<p>We talked with Guice about mixing the mystery and super hero elements together, crafting this tale with Coates and Harvey, and figuring out how the cast looks both in an out of costume.</p>,<p><strong>Marvel.com: Black Panther’s a great character in that he looks equally at home running around Wakanda as he does in Harlem. What would you say about his design that makes that so?</strong></p>,<p><strong>Butch Guice:</strong> Artistically, Black Panther is a very clean design. He’s got a little more detail in his costume now than in previous years but he is still essentially wearing a form-fitting masked body suit, which puts all the visual focus on how you handle his body language, athletic movement, [and] scene lighting. The character has been illustrated by some of the very best in the past so there is a high bar set in how to handle him.</p>,<p><strong>Marvel.com: This book also stars Misty Knight, Storm, Luke Cage, and Manifold. How do these characters play off of one another both in the quieter moments and the more action oriented ones?</strong></p>,<p><strong>Butch Guice:</strong> It is a great mix of characters—lots of variety in body types and personality—so at least for me, part of the pleasure of working on the book is playing with the variety I have within the team. One of the real joys of the job for me is deciphering characters, figuring out little subtle things about the way they move or dress or express themselves in conversation, and then trying to fully realize those extra layers of depth in the art.</p>,<p><strong>Marvel.com: Of this group, Manifold’s the newest character. Were there any challenges in getting him down from an artistic perspective?</strong></p>,<p><strong>Butch Guice:</strong> Not really. I was actually more familiar with Manifold than some of the others, having drawn him briefly during my run on [<a href="http://marvel.com/comics/series/17547/secret_avengers_2013_-_2014">SECRET AVENGERS</a>] a couple of years back. He’s got a great visual look thanks in part to his aboriginal background, especially when he is in street clothes.</p>,<p><em><a href="https://comicstore.marvel.com/Black-Panther-And-The-Crew-2017-1/digital-comic/44578">BLACK PANTHER AND THE CREW #1</a> dives into the mystery presented by Ta-Nehisi Coates, Yona Harvey and Butch Guice on April 12!</em></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://bijousfashions.biz/see-how-black-panther-and-his-new-team-come-together-in-harl/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9d84ccb7-cdfe-4876-82e4-eeccb7901b23</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 12:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday a batch of letters that Louis Armstrong wrote to a girlfriend will go on sale at an auction house in Los Angeles. That in itself is not surprising: Armstrong wrote thousands of letters in his lifetime, and he was known to be a lothario.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/2cd7a3ba-4e88-4d0c-9856-d7f3406c92b9.jpg">,<p>But these letters offer strong evidence of something else: Armstrong, who most biographers say was childless, believed until his death that he had a child. What’s more, the woman he regarded as his daughter has surfaced and says Armstrong supported her and her mother for more than 15 years, sending them monthly checks from his manager’s office, buying a house for them in Mount Vernon, N.Y, and even saving $25,000 for her college expenses.</p>,<p>“He died thinking in the back of his mind that he had a daughter out there,” said Ricky Riccardi, the archivist at the <a href="http://www.louisarmstronghouse.org/">Louis Armstrong House</a> Museum in Queens.</p>,<p>The woman, Sharon Preston-Folta, 57, of Sarasota, Fla., said she decided to break her long silence about what she calls “my parents’ secret” because she was upset that Armstrong’s estate never recognized her existence. His will left her family nothing, and his last wife, the former Lucille Wilson, signed an affidavit to the court stating that he had no children. Besides selling the letters, estimated to be worth as much as $80,000, she is releasing a short memoir on Kindle, written with Denene Millner.</p>,<p>“I chose to tell my story now because it’s about my legacy,” Ms. Preston-Folta said. “I matter. My story is important. I have every right to say who I am, to be proud of it.”</p>,<p>Ms. Preston-Folta, a media planner for a department-store chain who is married and has a grown son, bears a striking resemblance to Armstrong, but has no medical evidence to support her claims — just the letters and a sworn affidavit from her mother, who is 91 and declined to be interviewed.</p>,<p>Dear Dad,</p>,<p>I thought that telling our story would bring me some peace. I laid that burden, too, on time—thought that the passing years and the life experiences and the wisdom gained would make me feel better about our relationship. About you and I. About what we were not. But it hasn’t. Speaking our story out loud only brings more confusion and bitterness and anger. Mostly, it makes me incredibly sad.</p>,<p>I’m used to this lethal jumble of emotions, you know. For so very long, they’ve kept me numb—made my heart perform its function sans one of its most crucial human elements: feeling. Perhaps it’s in my DNA. The part I get from you. Or maybe it was learned—a defense mechanism slowly created across the span of missed birthdays, and Thanksgivings and Christmases, missed school and music recitals, missed moments of encouragement and discipline, a childhood devoid of hugs and kisses and reassurances that everything would be all right because Daddy would see to it that it was so. Absence does not make the heart grow fonder. It anesthetizes it. This, I know for sure.</p>,<p>Still, I love you. Because you are my father and I am your daughter and that is as it should be. And when I tamp down the unsettling emotions and push the darkness far into the recesses, there is some sliver of light that reminds me of all the things I loved about you—those big ol’ eyes, that hearty laugh, that wide, toothy grin, those long fingers and sturdy arms that I lived to fold into. The way that grumbly, froggy voice of yours sang out my name. <em>Sharon.</em> Recently, while I was helping my mother move, I found one of the many reel-to-reel tapes you made for her, and, to my surprise, it contained a personal message to Mom and me! You were in Germany making the film <em>Kisses In the Night</em> and recording the duet, “Uncle Satchmo’s Lullaby,” with an 11-year-old German girl named Gabrielli, and you said that she reminded you of me. Me! All the way in Germany, busy as you were, you were thinking about your daughter. Even as you scolded, warning me that you’d keep my presents if I weren’t a good girl and saying you were a tough daddy because you came up the hard way, I loved that you were talking right to me. And when you laughed that big, robust laugh and said I’d be getting my presents anyway, I laughed too. And then tears filled my eyes. I was both ecstatic and deeply saddened by that recording. It made me happy because it confirmed what I always knew: you were proud to be my dad—as much as I was, and am, proud to be your daughter. But that joy is diminished by your not being there.</p>,<p>See, the showing of the love—that’s what’s most necessary in a relationship between a parent and a child. Those tender moments, when there is no stage, when the spotlight isn’t shining, when nobody else is watching and documenting the hugs and the kisses and the simple things, like playing a board game together or snuggling on the couch, enjoying a TV show with one another, or sitting down for a family dinner—that’s what draws a child closer to you. You always took great care to remind me of the financial sacrifice you were making for me, and how you were working hard and far away for my own good. Because it was important for you to supply my needs. You did, and for that, I’m grateful. What I needed most, though, you refused. <em>I needed you.</em> Not socks full of coins. Not savings bonds. Not fancy presents purchased in random stores in Germany. Not recordings of you singing with other little girls and clipped warnings to be good, or else.</p>,<p>I. Needed. You.</p>,<p>Until now, I’ve been nothing more than an enigma—a footnote in your narrative, worthy, in some cases of not even a sentence. “He thinks he had a child…”—that’s what was written in the foreward of one book that chronicled in great detail your many writings. Funny: that book showcased a letter in which you explain in great detail how I was conceived, but in all the years since you’ve passed, in all the books that have been written by and about you, even in the midst of the making of an upcoming biopic directed by and starring Forest Whitaker, which promises to reveal new details about your life, no one’s ever bothered to see if I really exist. Those who did know—and there were many— made quick work after your death of making sure I stayed invisible. To erase my very existence. I often think back to the humiliating way Mom and I were treated when you died—being told not to attend your funeral. That I was denied the chance to pay my respects and give a proper goodbye to my own father was confusing as hell back then. Today, I think it a travesty—a disgusting display by a bunch of adults too heartless, greedy and mean to care that a 15-year-old child should be able to mourn her father. The pain of this sears.</p>,<p>Being rendered invisible hurts. I need you to know that. The impact manifested itself in so many destructive ways—promiscuity, abuse, teen pregnancy, poverty, depression, anger. My relationship with my mother has always been fractured. Tricky. We love each other deeply, sure. And, bad decisions, flaws and all, our bond is unshakeable. She is the only parent I had. But the edges are frayed when it comes to you. She’s so sad that I’ve written this book—wishes I could understand and honor her point of view on the matter. If it were up to her, I would have taken this secret to my grave.</p>,<p>But saying out loud that I am your child is not about her. It is about doing what is right for me. Asking me to keep secret our relationship is akin to asking me to burn the Louis Armstrong DNA that flows through my veins. It is impossible to do without destroying myself completely. I can’t—won’t—keep it to myself. I love you too much for that. Love me too much for that. I deserve to know my father. I deserve to know the Armstrong family. I deserve to know who I am. And I have the right to say it, too…</p>,<p>This passage is an excerpt from <em>Little Satchmo: Living In the Shadows Of My Father, Louis Daniel Armstrong</em>, written by Sharon Preston-Folta, daughter of the legendary jazz trumpeter Louis Armstrong, with MyBrownBaby’s own Denene Millner. <em><a href="http://www.amazon.com/LITTLE-SATCHMO-ebook/dp/B00ANUFND6/ref=sr_1_1_title_1_kin?s=books&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1363147941&amp;sr=1-1&amp;keywords=little+satchmo">Little Satchmo</a></em><a href="http://www.amazon.com/LITTLE-SATCHMO-ebook/dp/B00ANUFND6/ref=sr_1_1_title_1_kin?s=books&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1363147941&amp;sr=1-1&amp;keywords=little+satchmo"> is available for $2.99, exclusively on Kindle and iPad HERE.</a></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/363dd2e7-588e-4a01-b897-162c1e6bc7c1.jpg" title="Louis Armstrong Had A Child: A Daughter Claims Her DNA&mdash;And, Finally, Her Legacy">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1c8e55ad-018f-41a8-bcca-f3972304af29.jpg" title="Louis Armstrong  and Sharon Preston-Folta who claims to be his daughter ">]]></description>
            <link>http://bijousfashions.biz/on-saturday-a-batch-of-letters-that-louis-armstrong-wrote-to/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d518025d-5627-4608-b642-99b119c26eb9</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 10:42:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[That LOOK ...is it Confidence ?..Attitude ?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/dd8c35ee-9d4a-439b-8108-4f2827c95799.jpg" title="That LOOK ...is it Confidence ?..Attitude ?" alt="CONFIDENCE !!">,<p> That LOOK ...</p>,<p>If you project authentic confidence, it comes through in all ways. Your attitude, demeanor, body language, style and tone all reflect your internal state. Your inner alignment shines forth and is immediately obvious to all who are listening. This comes through in any media: in face-to-face settings, virtual communications, and video.<br>If you are projecting authority, but not really feeling it inside, this comes through as well. Participants in your audience will recognize that there is something missing. It may not be obvious instantly. But even a highly polished presence does not always carry the full conviction and authority that you desire.<br>According to academic research, a full 93% of what audiences perceive as confidence depends on body language and vocal quality. Imagine. That only leaves 7% of your impression relying on the content of your presentation.<br>By the way, this drives some people really nuts. In one training class, some people stormed out of the room, they were so perturbed by these statistics. They just couldn't let in that the verbal content of their talk was not 'all they needed' to show their research.<br>However, since you're reading still reading this and haven't left the room, my hunch is you're ready to accept the facts. This does not in any way diminish the importance of those 7%. You still need to verify facts, polish words, and carefully build your message.<br>Yet, we all have limited time. When preparing for a presentation, wouldn't it make sense to balance preparation time in parallel with the outcomes? If 93% of your message depends on body language and vocal quality, it stands to reason that preparation, practice and performance should be similarly weighted.<br>You and I know that's not the case. Nine times out of ten, professionals, subject matter experts, sales staff and senior executives do the opposite. We often invest 93% on the content. We obsess over punctuation and spelling. We get snagged finding the perfect word. We worry and torment ourselves searching for dramatic flow of ideas.<br>The challenge is many of these habits are not new. If you are at a part of your career where you've been at this for some time, your habits for preparing for a presentation have been acquired over time. If you are just starting out, you have habits from school that also may reinforce a focus on content over delivery.<br>It can take years to cultivate poor presentation habits. The good new is-it can take just a few days and precise feedback to change them. Often, working one-on-one with a presentation coach is the best investment of time and energy for busy professionals. A presentation coach, especially one who works virtually, enables you to upgrade your presentation habits to be highly functional.<br>If just one of the people in your audience recognizes your vision, and is inspired, motivated and engaged, your investment has paid off in multiples.<br>Ready to grow your presentation skills for maximum impact? If you are in a position to communicate ideas, express business visions, and influence public opinions, this investment in your habits and skills will be paid back a hundred times over or more.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://bijousfashions.biz/that-look-is-it-confidence-attitude/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">069da8e0-68a3-41e4-acb0-46348954d11d</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2016 23:22:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Psalm 61 English Standard Version (ESV)...]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="http://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?url=http%3A%2F%2Fdjsyftkogtech.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F76820132321%2Fpsalm-61-english-standard-version-esv-lead-me&src=https%3A%2F%2Fw.soundcloud.com%2Fplayer%2F%3Furl%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fapi.soundcloud.com%252Ftracks%252F134775898%26visual%3Dtrue%26liking%3Dfalse%26sharing%3Dfalse%26auto_play%3Dfalse%26show_comments%3Dfalse%26continuous_play%3Dfalse%26origin%3Dtumblr&type=text%2Fhtml&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&schema=tumblr" width="500" height="500" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>http://djsyftkogtech.tumblr.com/post/76820132321/psalm-61-english-standard-version-esv-lead-me</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">03b689f6-f461-4724-b32c-0cd6ba3fdf5c</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 06:42:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>